[
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Cash",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Supplies",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Inventory",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Account Receivables",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Bank",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Petty Cash",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Building ",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease Accumulated Depreciation - Equipment",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Office Equipment",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Factory Equipment",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  }
]
